Director sometimes too
And I have played murder mystery throughout the fall and we will continue in the spring
I got one on instagram because it was i got a little message about
Wouldn't we be able to see a little neighbor what it looks like in castles
On Kalmar
A little backstage above do before the show
What looks like and so on and
I did like this that I
I took my camera and then I told the ensemble that we would make a little movie about this
And they took on the task with bravur
This camera it it brought around between the ensemble members
I don't really know as much as has been filmed but they have
I have filmed a great deal and
This is completely unedited
And
Yes
Preparing into the last
What you will see now is then unedited
Cut from Kalmar Castle where we play Mogården
And do you think this is exciting and interesting then we play
Again now until spring 15 January 2022
Where are the eight performance
Can recommend it
Is a good Christmas present if it is now that you
Have a little idea to dry what to give to someone who has everything
So it is then would it work great with
Have much
You need Peter you need to do anything know you can
Stretch out the legs here take it easy
Fix it
Lets see
Now Vu has chased out all the ghosts out this room
Time for a little to drink
In other words
I think you should look like this all the time
Exactly, really my new hairstyle
Agree with
Now I will take them out now I will have to attract my little pile
We may hope that the next murder mystery that you may have these left
Yes
How are you going for you then
It's fine
We run some maud style here.
Really fancy I have to say
Nice looking
If you look at, you look at.
Here you stand and are looking
Seeking for the meaning of life
Far down in a box
What is it I have Joesfine, is that the one I have, huh?
I think so
I can accompany you so I will show you
So
Perfect
Cannon
We go on into the gray hall, precisely the one it will stand up there
But you who are tall and stately
There is no inner gauge in the cabinet
Okay
Take off your shoes
So
Pope
Have i tell you a story about P Ovel
Hello Hi, then he just goes on .....
Is it good
Yes, it works well there.
Yes, it was Povel Ramel .....
We will see what happens in here then.
(Waffle)
Are it you who spinn my socks
Socks
Chairs ... the socks are left .....
What is happening here now
Here are lots of secrets the secret shrine ... Well it wasn't .... it was a bomb attack ...
(Ticking sound)
The voltage increases
Someone can help me move the cords ...
I fill this with something drinkable
I keep up
Now let's see here ...
What playground we got today ...
Huge
Hubertus is not a man who takes a lot of space on this earth
No, a very modest character
Nice and kind
Something like that, then they'll be backwards
Tongue as lead
It is noticeable that Daniel is used to hard body work
So it is in the arm ... it might not know about ...
Why did Albert Maud give a bomb
He didn't.
I found it in his military trunk when he came morning.
He always brought presents with me, so I peeked in his bag ....
Found this one and knew it must be to me
You are not kind.
These tablets make me weak and insane and forgetful.
I forget everything after taking them.
Hubertus no, so yes my friend.
You just think so.
Give me the gun.
I don't think you know how to handle a gun.
Suddenly I hear a huge bang, and reflexively I get up ...
Bertil's death.
But, this was two years ago.
How can Daniel still remain in the military
Albert came walking from Bertil's direction ....
and in his hand he held
The rise.
The bombing staircase.
He replaced it
Yes, and I stood with my pants down, and Albert glowed like a mood.
You will be arched, what the only thing he got out.
And I guess you said the same thing back.
Five
Five what is Hubertus talking about?
But it was well five children
Albert was shot.
How should you explain it to the county governor
Well, eugenia .....
Why do you have ...
Uh, wait now.
Sit down.
Yes, my mother always said that women are cunning than skator.
Skator
Empty your bag on contents, scary, unpleasant skates.
Freja, stop.
See, how easily the county governor got your balance.
You must be prepared, if you are now as innocent as you say.
Running around with the murder weapon requires you to think before you answer.
So, come so we have interrogation with the county governor.
You don't have your tablets, then Wednesday morning.
It's dangerous for you, Hubertus.
You can die from heart attack
But, I get so lethargic in the head of them.
No, no, you will not be lethargic.
You become sharply thought like a herring.
Herring.
Herring is one of the most common fish varieties.
It lives on both sides of the Atlantic ....
Empty your bag on contents, aircraft.
You think you can fly, but you are just a stupid ostrich trying to hide what you have.
Then we are done how does it feel Madde
Well then, it feels a bit sad
It is the last for the fall
But we got back
We don't use it
Does someone use it
Well, it's Gurs Rucksack
But should everything be here or there
Here
No, there does not have to scoop it up
Yes yes but is it the box to the lights
Yes use it
Hello
Did you get with your Åsa up too or
I haven't seen Åsa
Then we'll scratch
But when do we have performance
The 15th
January 15
Great
(Waffle)
Hello
What did you do now
What is not visible is not there
(Laugh)
Away
What is the pill to put in
Pill pills
Well
What did you say Madde
Ghosts
Is it ghosts here
You feel like that
Do you feel it is ghosts here
No
Should it be left or
Although Eugenia looks like a ghost
I do not think so
Gur shall talk too much
Here then, we should try to get down all our stuff now before we should ....
.... have some break
Whose is it that Pippi's Rucksack
It's Gur's jacket.
It's a little candy sugar.
We can shut it down.
Hello
What do you come up with for something exciting
A table
Are you tired
Yes a little
We are in the process of packing our stuff together
It's not so much stuff here
We are ready for the fall.
But we will come to spring, or how
Jajemen
January.
January 15
Yes now everything is removed.
Has everyone picked up everything now
Yes
How nice